I'll tell you whether we've received our first payment from YouTube or not. Watch the video till the end.
I never thought Shiva would give me such a big surprise.  I didn't even
expect it.  Because I didn't know
when all this happened. I
thought, "Come on, sir," but Shiva suddenly came to me and
said, "Are you ready quickly?"  He said, "What's wrong with that?"
I also took the light, but
I brought a surprise gift for you
.  I
thought there was still a product for me, but you
know how happy I feel, okay, let me
tell you without locking you up,
we finally got our first payment from YouTube
.
Do you know how happy I felt? At that moment,
you might be thinking, "Is this all about money?" There's nothing like that. They
said that our bank would have an issue and that money wouldn't come from it.  And if we
get money from YouTube, we also have to answer questions if
someone asks us.
Even if we say that, if we have worked hard for so many days and
today we have achieved the result, then that is the only
happiness, right? We should celebrate such a good moment, right? That is
why
I will make payasam at home, but at the same
time, mommy and I are not there. I
went to my brother and said,
how much payment did I get from YouTube, how many dollars did I get,
how many days did it take, how
many dollars will I get money, I have
put it in a long video. It will be in my story.
Watch it once and subscribe.